They Were Britian's Commando Elite
Age of Heroes is a drama, action, thriller film directed by Adrian Vitoria.
The true story of the formation of Ian Fleming's 30 Commando
unit, a precursor for the elite forces in the U.K.
Maj. Jack Jones, played by Sean Bean.
Jensen, played by Izabella Miko.
Cpl. Bob Rains, played by Danny Dyer.
Lt. Cdr. Ian Fleming, played by James D'Arcy.
RMP Col. Archer, played by Sebastian Street.
Sgt. MacKenzie, played by William Houston.
Age of Heroes is a 2011 British war film directed by Adrian Vitoria.
The film is based on the real-life events of the formation of Ian
Fleming's 30 Commando unit during World War II.
The film was released in the United Kingdom in 2011.
The tone is emotional and intense.